Guide to the Vassar College Subject Files, 1864–2023
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Spanish, see also: V. C. Departments and Programs. Modern Languages; V. C. Departments and Programs. Hispanic Studies (Folder 11.30)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Spanish. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.31)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Urban Studies (Folder 11.32)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Urban Studies. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.33)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Women's Studies (Folder 11.34-11.35)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Women's Studies. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.36)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Women's Studies. Newsletter (Folder 11.37)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Zoology (Folder 11.38)
- V. C. Departments and Programs. Zoology. Lectures, programs, etc. (Folder 11.39)
- V. C. Development Group and/or Program and/or Office (Folder 11.40)
- V. C. Dickinson-Kayden Fund Lectures and Concerts (Folder 11.41)
- V. C. Dining Hall, see: V. C. Buildings Students
- V.C. Diplomas (Folder 11.42)
- V. C. Director of Special Projects, see: V. C. Special Projects, Office of
- V. C. Disadvantaged, Programs for (Folder 11.43)
- V. C. Divestment From South Africa (Folder 11.44)
- V. C. Dog Tombstones see: V. C. Faculty Dogs
- V. C. Donors (Folder 11.45)
- V. C. Dormitories (Folder 11.46)
- V. C. Drama, see: V. C. Departments Drama, V. C. Philalethean Society
- V. C. Dramatic Workshop, see: V. C. Vassar Dramatic Workshop
- V. C. Drugs (Folder 11.47)
- V. C. Drugs and Alcohol Task Force (Folder 11.48)
- V. C. Early Decision Plan, see: V. C. Faculty/ Committees/ Admission, Committee on
- V. C. East Asian Studies (Folder 11.49)
- V. C. Educational Services, Office of (Folder 11.50)
- V. C. Eighteenth-century Weekend (Folder 11.51)
- V. C. Eleanor Roosevelt Chair (Folder 11.52)
- V. C. Elections (Folder 11.53)
- V. C. Elevator (Folder 11.54)
- V. C. Elizabeth Bacon Custer Fund (Folder 11.55)
- V. C. Employee Records (Folder 11.56)
- V. C. Employees (general) (Folder 11.57-11.58)
- V. C. Employees. Clippings, see: Biographical File, following Z
- V. C. Employees. List (Folder 11.59)
- V. C. Employees. Union, see also: V. C. Staff Association (Folder 11.60)
- V. C. Employees. "White Angels" (Folder 11.61)
- V. C. Endowment (Folder 11.62-11.64)
- V. C. Endowment. Campaign of Seven Colleges, 1928 (Folder 11.65)
- V. C. Energy Conservation, see: V. C. Plant Operations
- V. C. Enrollment (Folder 11.66)
- V. C. Entertainment and Entertainers (Folder 11.67)
- V. C. Entrance Requirements, see: V. C. Faculty, Committees. Admission, Committee
- V. C. Environmental Science Program (Folder 11.68)
- V. C. Environmental Society, see: V. C. Vassar Environmental Society
- V. C. Equipment (Folder 11.69)
- V. C. Euthenics Institute, see: V. C. Institute of Euthenics (1926), V. C. Institute of Euthenics Lending Library, V. C. Vassar Summer Institute for Euthenics 1927-1941, V. C. Institute of Euthenics - Euthenics Alumnae Association 1929 -
- V. C. Evening Russian Program (Folder 11.70)
- V. C. Examinations - Reports (Folder 11.71)
- V. C. Exchange and Transfer Students, see: V. C. Students Exchange and Transfer
- V. C. Executives in Residence Programs (Folder 11.72)
- V. C. Exoteric Society (Folder 11.73)
- V. C. Experimental Program, see: V. C. Curriculum, V. C. Students Independent Study
- V. C. Experimental Theatre, see also: The V.C. Drama Department Collection, a separate collection which includes photographs, programs, flyers, and other materials related to the organization (Folder 12.1)
- [EMPTY] (Folder 12.2-12.6)
- V. C. Exploring Transfer Program, see: V. C. Dana, Charles A.
- V. C. Expressions (Folder 12.7)
- V. C. Extension Courses, see also: Adelphi and Vassar, Union and Vassar (Folder 12.8)
- V. C. Facilities Operations (Folder 12.9)
- V. C. Faculty. Restricted to Faculty Members - Administrative Procedures (Folder 12.10)
- V. C. Faculty (General) (Folder 12.11-12.12)
- V. C. Faculty. List, through 1936/1937 (Folder 12.13)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1937/1938-1939/1940 (Folder 12.14)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1940/1941-1949/1950 (Folder 12.15)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1950/1951-1959/1960 (Folder 12.16)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1960/1961-1969/1970 (Folder 12.17)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1970/1971-1974/1975 (Folder 12.18)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1975/1976-1979/1980 (Folder 12.19)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1980/1981-1985/1986 (Folder 12.20)
- V. C. Faculty. List, 1987/1988- (Folder 12.21)
- V. C. Faculty. Academic Affiliations (Folder 12.22)
- V. C. Faculty. Annuities (Folder 12.23)
- V. C. Faculty. Appointments (Folder 12.24)
- V. C. Faculty. Bibliography (general) (Folder 12.25)
- V. C. Faculty. Bibliography, to 1949 (Folder 12.26)
- V. C. Faculty. Bibliography, 1950-1964 (Folder 12.27)
- V. C. Faculty. Bibliography, 1965- (Folder 12.28)
- EMPTY (Folder 12.29)
- V. C. Faculty. By-laws (Folder 12.30)
- V. C. Faculty. Caricatures, see: V. C. Humor, caricatures etc.
- V. C. Faculty. Center (Folder 13.1)
- V. C. Faculty. Chairs, Endowed (Folder 13.2)
- V. C. Faculty. Children (Folder 13.3-13.5)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees, general - to 1959 (Folder 13.6)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees, general–1960- (Folder 13.7)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Academic Buildings (Folder 13.8)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Academic Honesty (Folder 13.9)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Academic Space and Faculty Work Load (Folder 13.10)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Admission., see also: V. C. Admissions..., to 1955 (Folder 13.11)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Admission, 1956-1964 (Folder 13.12)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Admission, 1965-1969 (Folder 13.13)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Admission, 1970- (Folder 13.14)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Advisory (Folder 13.15)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Advisory System (Folder 13.16)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Appeal (Folder 13.17)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Assessment (Folder 13.18-13.19)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Broadcasting (Folder 13.20)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Calendar Days (Folder 13.21)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Combined Drive (Folder 13.22)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Committee on Committees (Folder 13.23)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Comprehensive Planning, 1968- (Folder 13.24-13.26)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Conference with the Trustees (for material after 1967, see: V. C. Faculty. Committees. Faculty Policy and Conference Committee) (Folder 13.27)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Cooperative Houses (Folder 13.28)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Cooperative System (Folder 13.29)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Coordinating Committee (Folder 13.30)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Coordinating Committee on Educational Policy, 1957-1959 (Folder 13.31-13.32)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Curricular Policies (Folder 13.33)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Curriculum, 1944/1945 (Folder 13.34)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Curriculum, 1945/1946-1947/1948 (Folder 13.35)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Curriculum, 1948/1949-1959/1960 (Folder 13.36)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Curriculum, 1960/1961-Dec. 1969 (Folder 13.37)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Curriculum, 1970-1973 (Folder 14.1)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Curriculum, 1974- (Folder 14.2)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Cutting Problem (Folder 14.3)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Departmental Organization (Folder 14.4)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Displaced Scholars, see also: V. C. Refugees (Folder 14.5)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Economy (Folder 14.6)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Examinations (Folder 14.7)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Exchanges, see: Twelve College Program
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Faculty Appointments and Salary (Folder 14.8)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Faculty Compensation (Folder 14.9)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Faculty Policy and Conference (for material before 1967, see: V. C. Faculty Committees Conference with Trustees...) (Folder 14.10)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Faculty Procedure (Folder 14.11-14.12)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Fellows (Folder 14.13)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Fellowships and Graduate Study (Folder 14.14-14.17)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Field Work (Folder 14.18)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Films (Folder 14.19)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Foreign Study (Folder 14.20)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Freshman Year (Folder 14.21)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Graduate Study (Folder 14.22)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Housing (Folder 14.23)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Independent Program (Folder 14.24)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Joint Committee. for Reorganization of Student Government (Folder 14.25)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Joint Trustee-Administration Faculty (Folder 14.26)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Journal of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 14.27)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Leaves and Privileges (Folder 14.28)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Lectures (Folder 14.29)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Long-range Planning (Folder 14.30)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Marking System (Folder 14.31)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Mellon Committee (Folder 14.32)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Middle States Evaluation (Folder 14.33)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Overview Comm. for Self-Study (Folder 14.34)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Policy and Conference (Folder 14.35)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Prizes (Folder 14.36)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Publications (Folder 14.37)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Research (Folder 14.38-14.39)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Research (Leica Camera) (Folder 14.40)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Salaries (Folder 14.41)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Schedule (Folder 14.42)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Scholarships (Folder 14.43)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Senior Vacation (Folder 14.44)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Solicitation and Appeals (Folder 14.45)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Special Committee to consider the College Retirement Equities (Folder 14.46)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Special Service Project, Advisory (Folder 14.47)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Status of Women (Folder 14.48)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Student Affairs (Folder 14.49)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Students' Records and Honors (Folder 14.50)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Teacher Education (Folder 14.51)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Use of Academic Buildings (Folder 14.52)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Vassar Emergency (Folder 14.53)
- V. C. Faculty. Committees. Vocational Guidance (Folder 14.54)
- V. C. Faculty. Computers (Folder 14.55)
- V. C. Faculty. Dogs (Folder 15.1)
- C. Faculty. Exchanges (Folder 15.2)
- V. C. Faculty. Gardens, see: V. C. Garden Plots
- V. C. Faculty. Housing (Folder 15.3-15.4)
- V. C. Faculty. Insurance and other fringe benefits (Folder 15.5)
- V. C. Faculty. Leaves of Absence (Folder 15.6)
- [EMPTY] (Folder 15.7)
- V. C. Faculty. Non-academic Activities (Folder 15.8)
- V. C. Faculty. Pension (Folder 15.9)
- V. C. Faculty. Promotions (Folder 15.10)
- V. C. Faculty. Publications and Professional Activities, see: V. C. Faculty Bibliography
- V. C. Faculty. Receptions (Folder 15.11)
- V. C. Faculty. Retirement and Deaths (Folder 15.12)
- V. C. Faculty. Rules (Folder 15.13)
- V. C. Faculty. Salaries, see also: V. C. Faculty. Committees. Salaries (Folder 15.14-15.17)
- V. C. Faculty. Secretary (Folder 15.18)
- V. C. Faculty. Study Group (Folder 15.19)
- V. C. Faculty. Teaching Load (Folder 15.20)
- V. C. Faculty. Traveling expenses (Folder 15.21)
- V. C. Faculty. Voting List (Folder 15.22)
- V. C. Faculty Advisers (Folder 15.23)
- V. C. Faculty Blood Bank (Folder 15.24)
- V. C. Faculty Club (Folder 15.25-15.26)
- V. C. Faculty Fellows (Folder 15.27)
- V. C. Faculty Flower Fund (Folder 15.28)
- V. C. Faculty Forum (organized and introduced by the Chaplain) (Folder 15.29)
- V. C. Faculty Handbook (Folder 15.30)
- V. C. Faculty Houses, see also: V. C. Faculty. Committee. Housing, V. C. Faculty. Housing (Folder 15.31)
- V. C. Faculty in Local Politics (Folder 15.32)
- V. C. Faculty Marshal (Folder 15.33)
- V. C. Faculty Parlor (Folder 15.34)
- V. C. Faculty Play (Folder 15.35-15.36)
- V. C. Faculty Science Club (Folder 15.37)
- V. C. Fall Council (Folder 15.38)
- V. C. Famine Relief Committee (Folder 15.39)
- V. C. Farm (Folder 15.40)
- V. C. Farm Unit (Folder 15.41)
- V. C. Federal Work-study Program (Folder 15.42)
- V. C. Fellowships, see also: V. C. Students. Fellowships (Folder 15.43)
- V. C. Feminist Union (Folder 15.44)
- V. C. Ferry, Dexter M., Jr., - Chair (Folder 15.45)
- V. C. Ferry, Edith - Memorial Scholarship, see: V. C. Scholarships
- V. C. Fiction (Folder 15.46)
- V. C. Fidac Medal (Folder 15.47)
- V. C. Field Day (Folder 15.48)
- V. C. Field Work Office, see also: V. C. Off-campus Studies (1968 - ),V. C. Career Development and Field Work (1981 - ) (Folder 15.49-15.50)
- V. C. Film Club and Film Society and Film Workshop (Folder 15.51)
- V. C. Film Series (Folder 15.52)
- V. C. Finances, (folders and 1 paper binder) (Folder 15.53-15.55)
- V. C. Financial Aid Office (Folder 15.56)
- V. C. Financial Planning Committee, see: V. C. Finances
- V. C. Financial Planning, Joint College Committee on Long-Range, see: V. C. Joint College Committee on...
- V. C. Fires and Fire Alarm System (Folder 15.57)
- V. C. Five College Project, see also: Eight-college conference, Seven-college Conference, Twelve-college Program (Folder 15.58)
- V. C. Flag (Folder 15.59)
- V. C. Flora Doras (Folder 15.60)
- V. C. Folklore (Folder 15.61)
- V. C. Folklore Foundation (Folder 15.62)
- V. C. Food Co-operatives (Folder 15.63)
- V. C. Food Service, see also: V. C. Thanksgiving. Dinner Menus... (Folder 15.64)
- V. C. Ford Intern Program (Folder 15.65)
- V. C. Foreign Scholarship Drive (Folder 15.66)
- V. C. Foreign Students, see: V. C. Student, Foreign
- V. C. Form Manual (Folder 15.67)
- V. C. Founder's Day (General) (Folder 16.1)
- V. C. Founder's Day. Invitations (extra copies), 1868-1908; [SEE Founder's Day Records for more complete run] (Folder 16.2)
- V. C. Founder's Day. Plays and Songs (extra copies), 1946-1952; [SEE Founder's Day Records for more complete run] (Folder 16.3)
- V. C. Founder's Day. Programs (extra copies), 1867-1911; [SEE Founder's Day Records for full program run] (Folder 16.4)
- V. C. Founder's Day. Programs (extra copies), 1912-1916; [SEE Founder's Day Records for full program run] (Folder 16.5)
- V. C. Founder's Day. Programs (extra copies), 1917-1926; [SEE Founder's Day Records for full program run] (Folder 16.6)
- V. C. Founder's Day. Programs (extra copies), 1927-1948; [SEE Founder's Day Records for full program run] (Folder 16.7)
- [Empty] - SEE Founder's Day Records collection (Folder 16.08-16.14)
- V. C. Freshman Council, 1983/84- (Folder 16.15)
- V. C. Freshman Hygiene (Folder 16.16)
- V. C. Freshman Orientation (Folder 16.17)
- V. C. Freshman Seminars (Folder 16.18)
- V. C. Freshmen (Folder 16.19)
- V. C. Fudge (Folder 16.20)
- V. C. Funds (general), see also: V. C. Gifts and names of funds (Folder 16.21)
- V. C. Furness Prize (Folder 16.22)
- V. C. Furniture (Folder 16.23)
- V. C. Furniture Exchange (Folder 16.24)
- V. C. G-Stringers (Folder 16.25)
- V. C. Gambling, Fall 1978- (Folder 16.26)
- V. C. Garden Plots (Folder 16.27)
- V. C. Gardens, see: V. C. Campus, V. C. Garden Plots, V. C. Campus Shakespeare Garden
- V. C. Gaudeamus, see: V. C. Songs Gaudeamus
- V. C. Gates (Folder 16.28)
- V. C. Gavel (Folder 16.29)
- V. C. Gay/Lesbian/Bisexual..., see: V. C. Task Force...
- V. C. Gay People Alliance, see also: V. C. Bisexual, Gay and Lesbian Alliance (Folder 16.30)
- V. C. General Manager (Folder 16.31)
- V. C. General Manager (Air raid instructions) (Folder 16.32)
- V. C. German Club (Folder 16.33)
- V. C. Gifts and Bequests, undated to 1929 (Folder 16.34)
- V. C. Gifts and Bequests, 1930-1939 (Folder 16.35)
- V. C. Gifts and Bequests, 1940-1969 (Folder 16.36)
- V. C. Gifts and Bequests, 1970- (Folder 16.37)
- V. C. Glee Club (Folder 16.38)
- V. C. Gold Dusters (Folder 16.39)
- V. C. Golf Course (Folder 16.40)
- V. C. Gorilla (Folder 16.41)
- V. C. Gospel Choir (Folder 16.42)
- V. C. Governance of Vassar College (Folder 16.43-16.45)
- V. C. Graduate Center (Folder 17.1-17.2)
- V. C. Graduate Study (Folder 17.3)
- V. C. Granddaughter and Grandsons (Folder 17.4)
- V. C. Grants (Folder 17.4A)
- V. C. Greek Plays (Folder 17.5)
- V. C. Greek Plays. Antigone, 1893 (Folder 17.6)
- V. C. Green Haven Program (Folder 17.7)
- V. C. Greetings (Folder 17.8)
- V. C. Griffin (Charles) Lectures (Folder 17.9)
- V. C. Grounds, see: V. C. Campus
- V. C. Grocery Store (Folder 17.10)
- V. C. Group Travel (Folder 17.11)
- V. C. Guests (Folder 17.12)
- V. C. Gymnasium (Folder 17.13)
- V. C. Halls, Dept of. (Folder 17.14)
- V. C. Handcrafts Studio, see also: V. C. Craft Shops (Folder 17.15)
- V. C. Handicapped Students Association (Folder 17.16)
- V. C. Harriot Stanton Club (Folder 17.17)
- V. C. Hazing, Accusations of (Folder 17.18)
- V. C. Health Services (Folder 17.19)
- V. C. Heating Plant (Folder 17.20)
- V. C. Helen Gates Putnam Conservation Fund, see: V. C. Departments Conservation, Division of
- V. C. Helen Gates Putnam Lectures (Folder 17.21)
- V. C. Helen Kenyon Lectures, (copies of) (Folder 17.22)
- V. C. Helen Kenyon Lectureship (Folder 17.23)
- V. C. Herbarium (Folder 17.24)
- V. C. Hillel, see also: V. C. Vassar Jewish Student Union (Folder 17.25)
- V. C. History (Folder 17.26-17.28)
- V. C. Holidays (Folder 17.29)
- V. C. Honor System (Folder 17.30)
- V. C. House Fellows (Folder 17.31)
- V. C. House Libraries (Folder 17.32)
- V. C. Housing, Faculty, see: V. C. Faculty. Committees. Housing, V. C. Faculty Housing
- V. C. Housing Seminar (Folder 17.33)
- V. C. Humor, Caricatures, etc., see also: V. C. Sophomore Joke Book (Folder 17.34)
- V. C. Hunger Action Committee (Folder 17.35)
- V. C. Hymnal (Folder 17.36)
- V. C. Independent Programs (includes Critical Languages, Latin American Studies, Medieval Studies, Renaissance Studies, Victorian Studies, etc.) (Folder 17.37)
- V. C. Information for New Students (Folder 17.38)
- V. C. Information for Parents (Folder 17.39)
- V. C. Institute, see: V. C. Vassar Summer Institute
- V. C. Institute for the Advancement of College and University Teaching (Folder 17.40)
- V. C. Institute of Earth Science, see: Summer Institute in Geology
- V. C. Institute of Euthenics, see also: V. C. Vassar Summer Institute, 1926 (Folder 17.41-17.42)
- V. C. Institute of Euthenics. Euthenics Alumnae Association, 1929 - (Folder 17.43)
- V. C. Institute of Euthenics. Lending Library (Inc. Van Horne Gift) (Folder 17.44)
- V. C. Institute of Geology, see: Summer Institute in Geology
- V. C. Institute of Progressive Education (Folder 17.45)
- V. C. Institutes, see: Institute for New York State High School Teachers of English, Summer Institute in Geology Summer Science Training Program in Chemistry
- V. C. Institutional Research Office (Folder 17.46)
- V. C. Insurance, health (Folder 17.47)
- V. C. Inter-club Council (Folder 17.48)
- V. C. Intercollegiate Conferences, see also: V. C. Conferences held at Vassar (Folder 17.49)
- V. C. Intercollegiate Disarmament Conference, October 22, 192l (Folder 17.50)
- V. C. Intercollegiate Socialist Society (Folder 17.51)
- V. C. Intercultural Center (Folder 17.52)
- V. C. Interdepartmental Courses and miscellaneous cooperative efforts (Folder 18.1)
- V. C. Interdepartmental Courses. The River (Folder 18.2)
- V. C. Interfaith Council (Folder 18.3)
- V. C. International Students (Folder 18.4)
- V. C. International Studies Program (Folder 18.5)
- V. C. International Studies Program. Lectures, etc., auspices of (Folder 18.6)
- V. C. Interns (Folder 18.7)
- V. C. Janitor (Folder 18.8)
- V. C. Jewish Studies, see also: Vassar Jewish Union (Folder 18.9)
- V. C. Joint Ad-Hoc Committee. On year round Operation (Folder 18.10)
- V. C. Joint College Committee on Long-Range Financial Planning (Folder 18.11)
- V. C. Joint Committee of Trustees, Faculty and Alumnae on Administration of V. C. (Folder 18.12)
- V. C. Joint Faculty-Student Self-Help Committee (Folder 18.13)
- V. C. Joint Trustee-Administration Committee on Salaries, Promotions and Sources of Funds (Folder 18.14)
- V. C. Joint Trustee-Faculty-Administration Committee (Folder 18.15)
- V. C. Journalism Forum see also: V. C. Poynter Fund, 1978- (Folder 18.16)
- V. C. Junior-Senior Excursions, see also: V. C. Boat ride ("Mary Powell") (Folder 18.17)
- V. C. Junior Year Abroad (Folder 18.18)
- V. C. Key Center (Folder 18.19)
- V. C. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Award for Community Service (Folder 18.20)
- V. C. Lesbian and Gay Alumnae/i of Vassar College (LAGA - VC) (Folder 18.21)
- V. C. Lady Principal (Folder 18.22)
- V. C. Lake Minnewaska Conferences. 1st (Folder 18.23)
- V. C. Lake Minnewaska Conferences. 2nd, 3rd (Folder 18.24)
- V. C. Lakes (Mill Cove, Sunset and Vassar combined in one folder) (Folder 18.25)
- V. C. Lamport Prize (Folder 18.26)
- V. C. Languages, Study of (Folder 18.27)
- V. C. Laundry, see also: V. C. Buildings Computer Center, V. C. Buildings Laundry (Folder 18.28)
- V. C. Laura J. Wylie Fund (Folder 18.29)
- V. C. Leadership Training for Wartime Community Services (Folder 18.30)
- V. C. Lecturers and Visitors. Moynihan, see also: 1990 Main Takeover Records (Folder 18.31)
- V. C. Lectures, see also: V. C. Chapel Services (Sermons), V. C. Lecture-series by title, V. C. Student Lecture Series, V. C. Vassar Scholars' Lectures (Folder 18.32-18.37)
- V. C. Lectures - Arnold, Matthew (Folder 18.38)
- V. C. Lectures - Emerson (Folder 18.39)
- V. C. Letterheads (Folder 18.40)
- V. C. Liberalism (Folder 18.41)
- V. C. Librarians (Folder 18.42)
- V. C. Libraries (General) (Folder 18.43-18.47)
- V. C. Libraries. Accession Numbers (Folder 18.48)
- V. C. Libraries. Building. (Frederick Ferris) Thompson Memorial Library. Floor Plans (Folder 18.49)
- V. C. Libraries. Building. (Frederick Ferris) Thompson Memorial Library. Orig. Building, 1905 (Folder 18.50)
- V. C. Libraries. Building. (Frederick Ferris) Thompson Memorial Library. Remodeling, 1960 (Folder 18.51)
- V. C. Libraries. Building. (Martha Rivers and E. Bronson) Ingram Library, 1997 (Folder 18.51a)
- V. C. Libraries. Building. (Helen D.) Lockwood. Library, 1976 (Folder 18.52)
- V. C. Libraries. Card Catalog (Folder 18.53)
- V. C. Libraries. Chinese Bronze Wall Plaque (Folder 18.54)
- V. C. Libraries. Conferences and Special Activities (Folder 18.55)
- V. C. Libraries. Courses (Folder 18.56)
- V. C. Libraries. Curtis Lecture (Folder 18.57)
- V. C. Libraries. Curtis Lecture: DeMaria, Robert (Folder 18.58)
- V. C. Libraries. Donors (Folder 18.59)
- V. C. Libraries. Exhibitions and hours (Folder 19.1)
- V. C. Libraries. Founding Friends of the Library (Folder 19.2)
- V. C. Libraries. Friends of the Library (Folder 19.3)
- V. C. Libraries. Handbooks: see catalogued volumes: Z733.V37 H36
- V. C. Libraries. Handicapped Services (Folder 19.4)
- V. C. Libraries. Library Committee (Folder 19.5)
- V. C. Libraries. Library Log (Folder 19.6)
- V. C. Libraries. Media Resources (Folder 19.6a)
- V. C. Libraries. Music Library (Folder 19.7)
- V. C. Libraries. Newsletter (Folder 19.8)
- V. C. Libraries. Personnel (Folder 19.9)
- V. C. Libraries. Postcards (Folder 19.10)
- V. C. Libraries. Printers' Marks (Folder 19.11)
- V. C. Libraries. Reading Suggestions for Refugees (Folder 19.12)
- V. C. Libraries. Rules and Regulations (Folder 19.13)
- V. C. Libraries. Special Collections (Folder 19.14)
- V. C. Libraries. Statistics (Folder 19.15)
- V. C. Libraries. Tapestries (Folder 19.16)
- V. C. Libraries. Town Hall Reading Lists (Folder 19.17)
- V. C. Libraries. Vassariana (Folder 19.18)
- V. C. Libraries. Window (Folder 19.19-19.20)
- V. C. Listening Center (students counseling students) (Folder 19.21)
- V. C. (Frances Lehman) Loeb Art Center (Folder 19.22)
- V. C. Luce Program (Folder 19.23)
- V. C. Luce Scholars (Folder 19.24)